Omar Stewart

housekeeping - Global Spectrum

- Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Omar-Stewart/2dd0486888e8f494

I am flexible and dependable with 5+ years of housekeeping & customer service experience. I am seeking a position in a company that utilizes my abilities and skills and which will promote individual opportunity and professional growth.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

housekeeping

Global Spectrum - Philadelphia, PA - September 2010 to Present

- Detail Cleaning
- Hard floor care
- Operating walk-behind/ride-on scrubbers
- Carpet Cleaning

Cashier

Walmart - Philadelphia, PA - November 2007 to February 2010

- · Receive payment by cash, cheques, credit card etc
- Checking daily cash accounts
- Providing training and assistance to new joined cashier

Packer/Receiver

- Packs outgoing sales orders and return merchandise authorizations
- · Checks product pulled against order
- Packs product to meet shipping requirements
- · Assists with month-end inventory

Cook

Chic-Fil-A - Philadelphia, PA - June 2006 to August 2007

- Perform guest service
- Food preparation dities
- Unloading deliveries
- · Maintaining a clean store environment

EDUCATION

South Philadelphia High School E.O.P - Philadelphia, PA 2015 to 2016

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS

Well organized, able to prioritize and meet deadlines

- Able to work within a team and with little or no supervision
- Able to communicate and understand both written and verbally
- Able to adapt to often changing, face paced environment, following policies and procedures set forth